[
  {
    "Front": "Año",
    "Back": "Year",
    "Order": 1
  },
  {
    "Order": 2,
    "Front": "más",
    "Back": "more"
  },
  {
    "Order": 3,
    "Front": "Ciudad",
    "Back": "City"
  },
  {
    "Order": 4,
    "Front": "Baño",
    "Back": "Bathroom"
  },
  {
    "Order": 5,
    "Front": "Escuela",
    "Back": "School"
  },
  {
    "Order": 6,
    "Front": "Aquí",
    "Back": "Here"
  },
  {
    "Order": 7,
    "Front": "Película",
    "Back": "Movie"
  },
  {
    "Order": 8,
    "Front": "Familia",
    "Back": "Family"
  },
  {
    "Order": 9,
    "Front": "Tener",
    "Back": "to have"
  },
  {
    "Order": 10,
    "Front": "Hablar",
    "Back": "to talk"
  },
  {
    "Order": 11,
    "Front": "Gustar",
    "Back": "to like"
  },
  {
    "Order": 12,
    "Front": "Nuevo",
    "Back": "new"
  },
  {
    "Order": 13,
    "Front": "Siempre",
    "Back": "always"
  },
  {
    "Order": 14,
    "Front": "Antigua",
    "Back": "old"
  },
  {
    "Order": 15,
    "Front": "Bueno",
    "Back": "good"
  },
  {
    "Order": 16,
    "Front": "Fácil",
    "Back": "easy"
  },
  {
    "Order": 17,
    "Front": "Difícil",
    "Back": "difficult"
  },
  {
    "Order": 18,
    "Front": "Alto",
    "Back": "high"
  },
  {
    "Order": 19,
    "Front": "Cerca",
    "Back": "near"
  },
  {
    "Order": 20,
    "Front": "Pero",
    "Back": "but"
  },
  {
    "Order": 21,
    "Front": "Porque",
    "Back": "because"
  },
  {
    "Order": 22,
    "Front": "ahora",
    "Back": "now"
  },
  {
    "Order": 23,
    "Front": "cuando",
    "Back": "when"
  },
  {
    "Order": 24,
    "Front": "hacer",
    "Back": "to do, to make"
  },
  {
    "Order": 25,
    "Front": "nunca",
    "Back": "never"
  },
  {
    "Order": 26,
    "Front": "dónde",
    "Back": "where"
  },
  {
    "Order": 27,
    "Front": "verdad",
    "Back": "truth"
  },
  {
    "Order": 28,
    "Front": "Hoy",
    "Back": "today"
  },
  {
    "Order": 29,
    "Front": "Mañana",
    "Back": "tomorrow"
  },
  {
    "Order": 30,
    "Front": "Ayer",
    "Back": "yesterday"
  },
  {
    "Order": 31,
    "Front": "Después",
    "Back": "after"
  },
  {
    "Order": 32,
    "Front": "Sitio",
    "Back": "place"
  },
  {
    "Order": 33,
    "Front": "País",
    "Back": "country"
  },
  {
    "Order": 34,
    "Front": "Este/Esto/Esta",
    "Back": "\"This\" or \"This one\""
  },
  {
    "Order": 35,
    "Front": "Ese/ Eso/Esa",
    "Back": "\"That\" or \"That one\""
  },
  {
    "Order": 36,
    "Front": "Coche",
    "Back": "car"
  },
  {
    "Order": 37,
    "Front": "Idioma",
    "Back": "language"
  },
  {
    "Order": 38,
    "Front": "Mujer",
    "Back": "woman"
  },
  {
    "Order": 39,
    "Front": "Hombre",
    "Back": "man"
  },
  {
    "Order": 40,
    "Front": "Ver",
    "Back": "to see"
  },
  {
    "Order": 41,
    "Front": "Dar",
    "Back": "to give"
  },
  {
    "Order": 42,
    "Front": "Llevar",
    "Back": "to carry"
  },
  {
    "Order": 43,
    "Front": "Encontrar",
    "Back": "to find"
  },
  {
    "Order": 44,
    "Front": "Decir",
    "Back": "to tell"
  },
  {
    "Order": 45,
    "Front": "Venir",
    "Back": "to come"
  },
  {
    "Order": 46,
    "Front": "Pensar",
    "Back": "to think"
  },
  {
    "Order": 47,
    "Front": "Leer",
    "Back": "to read"
  },
  {
    "Order": 48,
    "Front": "Trabajar",
    "Back": "to work"
  },
  {
    "Order": 49,
    "Front": "Usar",
    "Back": "to use"
  },
  {
    "Order": 50,
    "Front": "Alguno",
    "Back": "some"
  },
  {
    "Order": 51,
    "Front": "Bajo",
    "Back": "low"
  },
  {
    "Order": 52,
    "Front": "Nunca",
    "Back": "never"
  },
  {
    "Order": 53,
    "Front": "También",
    "Back": "also"
  }
]